<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Platzigram</string>
    <string name="username">Usuario</string>
    <string name="password">Contraseña</string>
    <string name="login">Iniciar sesión</string>
    <string name="not_registered_question">¿No tienes cuenta?</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Regístrate</string>
    <string name="email">Correo electrónico</string>
    <string name="name">Nombre</string>
    <string name="password_confirm">Confirma contraseña</string>
    <string name="sign_up_cta">Únete</string>
    <string name="title_sign_up">Registro</string>
    <string name="elapsed_time_pre">Hace</string>
    <string name="elapsed_time">4</string>
    <string name="elapsed_time_pos">días</string>
    <string name="likes_qty">10</string>
    <string name="like">Me Gusta</string>
    <string name="title_explore">Explorar</string>
    <string name="title_timeline">Inicio</string>
    <string name="title_profile">Yo</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_reference">ReferenceActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">"Material is the metaphor.\n\n"</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="lorem">Bacon ipsum dolor amet pork meatball buffalo, swine burgdoggen kielbasa ribeye chicken rump turkey brisket. Ham t-bone leberkas, ground round prosciutto pork salami porchetta pancetta picanha fatback ball tip sirloin pork chop swine. Tenderloin landjaeger t-bone, pig andouille jowl cow bacon porchetta shoulder pancetta ham hock. Sirloin ham chuck pork loin strip steak, pork rump cupim bresaola landjaeger chicken ham hock jerky hamburger.  \nPork loin sirloin ham doner shank brisket alcatra. Filet mignon pancetta jowl turducken. Meatball landjaeger ball tip porchetta hamburger ground round chuck chicken cow short loin sirloin short ribs leberkas tenderloin. Chicken doner pork chop, porchetta tenderloin ball tip jerky fatback leberkas spare ribs pancetta. Fatback short loin ham hock ground round, kielbasa hamburger brisket ham chicken tail. Corned beef beef ham hock, capicola bacon frankfurter tongue. Brisket tenderloin ball tip sirloin meatball landjaeger drumstick chuck cupim capicola pork belly.  \nShank corned beef swine ribeye tongue sirloin sausage t-bone drumstick cow biltong. T-bone porchetta leberkas pancetta pork chop salami meatloaf jerky brisket cupim corned beef alcatra rump picanha. Beef ribs ribeye picanha jerky, sausage fatback short ribs meatloaf filet mignon swine. Beef ribs bacon andouille shoulder, ribeye ham brisket venison tongue cupim jerky meatball. Bacon fatback cupim, boudin landjaeger picanha swine cow meatloaf hamburger pig ground round.  \nVenison boudin salami prosciutto short ribs, turducken drumstick turkey porchetta kevin rump biltong. Filet mignon bresaola kevin shoulder landjaeger cupim corned beef beef bacon ham hock prosciutto turducken ball tip boudin. Spare ribs short loin bresaola alcatra prosciutto tenderloin cupim pancetta capicola filet mignon doner andouille drumstick t-bone. Hamburger chuck meatball, shankle jerky pork loin ground round corned beef picanha short loin salami pork chop bresaola andouille. Buffalo ham t-bone landjaeger beef swine rump pig tri-tip cupim short ribs meatball.  \nMeatball pig shankle, t-bone alcatra hamburger leberkas pork belly short loin. Tri-tip jerky pork loin brisket bresaola. Sirloin shoulder salami, bacon tongue pork belly pork hamburger. Turkey kielbasa landjaeger ball tip salami, pancetta cow.</string>
</resources>
